var questions = [{
    "question": "Modern mountain bikes have what type of brakes?",
    "option1": "Rim brakes",
    "option2": "Disc brakes",
    "option3": "Emergency brakes",
    "option4": "Drum brakes",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "What is the name of the common device that changes your gears on a mountain bike?",
    "option1": "Changer",
    "option2": "Derailleur",
    "option3": "Shifter",
    "option4": "Gear Thing",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "Which one of these is NOT a brand of Mountain Biking apparel?",
    "option1": "Fox",
    "option2": "Troy Lee Designs",
    "option3": "Dakine",
    "option4": "Quiksilver",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    "question": "Which one of these is NOT a Mountain Bike brand?",
    "option1": "Kona",
    "option2": "All three are an MTB brand",
    "option3": "Commencal",
    "option4": "Intense",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "What is the world's largest Mountain Bike component brand?",
    "option1": "SRAM",
    "option2": "Avid",
    "option3": "Hayes",
    "option4": "Shimano",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    "question": "What term do Mountain Bikers use when in the lowest gear on a bike?",
    "option1": "Granny Gear",
    "option2": "1st Gear",
    "option3": "Girly Gear",
    "option4": "Easy Gear",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question": "What are the names of the metal wires that run from the hub to the rim of the wheel?",
    "option1": "Rear Brakes",
    "option2": "Forks",
    "option3": "Stems",
    "option4": "Spokes",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    "question": "What is the name of the part of a bicycle frame that the fork steerer passes through?",
    "option1": "Top Tube",
    "option2": "Head Tube",
    "option3": "Down Tube",
    "option4": "Bottom Bracket",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "To which part of the bicycle is the tyre mounted?",
    "option1": "Hub",
    "option2": "Spoke",
    "option3": "Rim",
    "option4": "Seat Stay",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "Where is the RED BULL RAMPAGE held at?",
    "option1": "ANZ Stadium",
    "option2": "Grand Canyon",
    "option3": "Tokyo, Japan",
    "option4": "Zion National Park in Virgin",
    "answer": "4"
},
]